Guide to the University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees, Meeting Minutes, 1845-present UA.1.4
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Supporting Documentation, June 4, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Regular Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 4, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Western Pennsylvania Medical College Graduate List, October 1906 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 30, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, Feburary 15, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Supporting Documentation, February 15, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 7, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 12, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Supporting Documentation, April 12, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Carnegie Institute Dedication Program, April 11-13, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 3, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 7, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Supporting Documentation, June 7, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 3, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 29, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 13, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Supporting Documentation, December 13, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 5, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Supporting Documentation, March 5, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 1908 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 1, 1908; 1.
  - Western University of Pennsylvania, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 8, 1908; 2.
- Western University of Pennsylvania, Supporting Documentation, June 1908 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 27, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 1908 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 1, 1908; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 2, 1908; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 2, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 19, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 19, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 6, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, November 6, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- University of Pittsburgh, University Bulletin, September 1908 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- University of Pittsburgh, University Bulletin, October 1908 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 16, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, January 16, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 4, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 4, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 8, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 7, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 7, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 11, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 25, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 9, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, July 9, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 16, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, July 16, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, September-October 7, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 16, 1909; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 7, 1909; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 21, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 21, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 11, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, November 11, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 29, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 3, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, October 3, 1907-February 3, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Membership Suggestion List (Box 4, Folder 50)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 3, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 3, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June-December, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 6, 1910; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 10, 1910; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 15, 1910; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 10, 1910; 4.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 12, 1910; 5.
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June-December, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 13, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, March 13, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 12, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 12, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 14-July, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 14, 1911; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 24, 1911; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, July 24, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 9, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, October 9, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 11, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, December 11, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 26, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, January-March, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 15, 1912; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 21, 1912; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 11, 1912; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, January-March, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June-July, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 10, 1912; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 19, 1912; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 12, 1912; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June-July, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 14, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, November 1912-March 10, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 3, 1912; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 9, 1912; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 28, 1913; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 10, 1913; 4.
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 24, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1910-1913 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 1913 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 9, 1913; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 16, 1913; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, September-October 1913 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 17, 1913; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 13, 1913; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 1913-March 1914 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 8, 1913; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 9, 1914; 2.
- Indentures from the Sale of the Kaufmann Clinic, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June-October 12, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 8, 1914; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 16, 1914; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 12, 1914; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 26, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 14, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 21, 1914-March 1915 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 21, 1914; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 8, 1915; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 15, 1915; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, May-June, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 17, 1915; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 14, 1915; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 14, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 11, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 1915-March 2, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 13, 1915; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 2, 1916; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March 1916 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 13, 1916; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 20, 1916; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, June 1913-March 1916 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June-October 10, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 12, 1916; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 10, 1916; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 31, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 12, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March-June 1917 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 13, 1917; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 20, 1917; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 12, 1917; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October-December 1917 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 9, 1917; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 11, 1917; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 15, 1917; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March-May, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 12, 1918; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 29, 1918; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June-August, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 11, 1918; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 18, 1918; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 2, 1918; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, August 2, 1918; 4.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 1918-March 1919 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 8, 1918; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 10, 1918; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 13, 1918; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 24, 1918; 4.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 11, 1919; 5.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 25, 1919; 6.
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, April-July 1919 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 22, 1919; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 10, 1919; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 9, 1919; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, April-July, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 23, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 1919 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 7, 1919; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 14, 1919; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Annual Reports of the Treasurer and Auditor, June 30, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, December 1919 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Univeristy of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 9, 1919; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 16, 1919; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, February-April 1920 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 12, 1920; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 5, 1920; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 9, 1920; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 26, 1920
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes Index, 1916-1920 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, May-June 8, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 11, 1920; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 8, 1920; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, May 11, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 29, 1920-March 8, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 29, 1920; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 12, 1920; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 1, 1920; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 15, 1920; 4.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 14, 1920; 5.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 8, 1921; 6.
- University of Pittsburgh, Supporting Documentation, June 29, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, March 24, 1921-November 17, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 24, 1921; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 14, 1921; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 16, 1921; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 11, 1921; 4.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 13, 1921; 5.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Informal Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 17, 1921; 6.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, November 22, 1921-March 14, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 22, 1921; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 13, 1921; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 14, 1922; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 17, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 1922-May 4, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 13, 1922; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 10, 1922; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 12, 1922; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, February 5, 1923; 4.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 13, 1923; 5.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 4, 1923; 6.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, May 24 and June 12, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 24, 1923; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 12, 1923; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 20 and July 19, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 20, 1923; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, July 19, 1923; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October-December, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 9, 1923; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 13, 1923; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 11, 1923; 3.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, January-March, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 10, 1924; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Spring Meeting of the Board of Trustees, March 11, 1924; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, April-June 10, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, April 14, 1924; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, May 15, 1924; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 9, 1924; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 10, 1924; 4.
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, June 26 and September 19, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, June 26, 1924; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, September 19, 1924; 2.
- University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 14, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- University of Pittsburgh, Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, October 1924-March 1925 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - University of Pittsburgh, Fall Meeting of the Board of Trustees, October 14, 1924; 1.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, November 19, 1924; 2.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Winter Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 9, 1924; 3.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Adjourned Meeting of the Board of Trustees, December 16, 1924; 4.
  - University of Pittsburgh, Special Meeting of the Board of Trustees, January 6, 1925; 5.